<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My GamePix Games</title>
    <description>Games from GamePix ecosystem.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:05:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>GamePix</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <link>https://www.gamepix.com</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://feeds.gamepix.com/v1/xml?order=quality&amp;page=1&amp;pagination=12&amp;sid=P5705"/>
    <atom:link rel="next" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://feeds.gamepix.com/v1/xml?order=quality&amp;page=2&amp;pagination=12&amp;sid=P5705"/>
    
    <atom:link rel="last" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://feeds.gamepix.com/v1/xml?order=quality&amp;page=523&amp;pagination=12&amp;sid=P5705"/>
    <atom:link rel="first" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://feeds.gamepix.com/v1/xml?order=quality&amp;page=1&amp;pagination=12&amp;sid=P5705"/>
    <item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/flamit/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Flamit</title>
  <description>Light all the torches as fast as you can in this engaging platform.
But do it fast, because a your flame won&apos;t last forever!
Featuring:
- 30 one-screen levels full of funny obstacles
- 2 Different game mode
- spikes
- ice enemies
- more spikes
- snow
- A lot of torches

Controls
Touch the screen controls or use arrow keys to move the Player

- 30 one-screen levels full of funny obstacles
- 2 Different game mode
- spikes
- ice enemies
- more spikes
- snow
- A lot of torches</description>
  <category>adventure</category>
  <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 10:39:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/cerkio/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Cerkio</title>
  <description>Touch the screen at the right time to throw the ball in the white circle.
Repeat it for more than 30 levels and prove yourself you are skilled enough to complete the game!

34 levels
Nice music
Relaxing game
one hand game</description>
  <category>ball</category>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:43:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/skibidi-laser-kill/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Skibidi Laser Kill</title>
  <description>Skibidi Laser Kill Game is a fast-paced, action-packed laser shooter arcade game. Players take control of a laser-wielding character and must defend themselves against waves of oncoming enemies. The game features a variety of enemies, each with their own unique attacks. Players must use their skills and reflexes to dodge enemy fire and take them down. </description>
  <category>action</category>
  <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 09:31:57 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/royal-couple-halloween-party/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Royal Couple Halloween Party</title>
  <description>Welcome to Royal Couple Halloween Party. Halloween is behind the corner and your favorite Royal couples are getting ready to go trick-or-treating in their great fantasy world. Browse their wardrobe for perfect costumes for each couple. Come and join the girls and see what highly original Halloween costumes you can create for each of them. Have fun, ladies!</description>
  <category>kids</category>
  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 10:12:17 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/penalty-kick-wiz/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Penalty Kick Wiz</title>
  <description>Penalty Kick Wiz is a penalty shooter arcade game to kick the soccer ball and shoot to the scoring goal. Become a master of penalty shooters!</description>
  <category>sports</category>
  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 10:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/sokoballs/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Sokoballs</title>
  <description>Sokoballs is a classic puzzle game deeply inspired by puzzle games like Sokoban. In this game you have to place all the balls on the switches you can find in each level.  Use the arrow keys or WASD to move the player. If you get stuck press R to restart the level.</description>
  <category>ball</category>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 16:13:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/body-drop-3d/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Body Drop 3D</title>
  <description>The game will delight you with a realistic simulation of the body falling! Its advantage is not only physics, but also the realistic behavior of the character, his animations, nice graphics and many levels!</description>
  <category>action</category>
  <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 14:26:01 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/yummy-toast/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Yummy Toast</title>
  <description>Yummy Toast is the funnest cooking game ever!
Your goal is to make delicious toast by tapping the correct materials and ingredients u needed. Make the tastiest toast and serve to ur customers. Be the best toast master and to unlock all the achievements!</description>
  <category>kids</category>
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 08:31:09 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/turbo-dismounting/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Turbo Dismounting</title>
  <description>Turbo Dismounting Stickman game</description>
  <category>mobile</category>
  <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 14:59:41 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/kobadoo-shapes/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Kobadoo Shapes</title>
  <description>Kobadoo Shapes is a browser game that trains your brain by memorizing coloured geometric shapes in the right order.

When you play Kobadoo Shapes you are actively using your working memory. Several scientific studies suggest that training of working memory has beneficial effects and can increase your cognitive functions.

Full version: https://www.kobadoo.com</description>
  <category>trivia</category>
  <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 13:55:23 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/morphit/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Morphit</title>
  <description>Morphit is a hypercasual game where you have to change your shape to pass trough the obstacles.
Try to last as long as you can and unlock all the achievements!
Game Controls:
touch the buttons to change the shape of the player and match the obstacles&apos;ones.</description>
  <category>arcade</category>
  <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 10:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://play.gamepix.com/kobadoo-flags/embed?sid=P5705</guid>
  <title>Kobadoo Flags</title>
  <description>Kobadoo Flags is a browser game that trains your brain by memorizing flags of the World in the right order.

When you play Kobadoo Flags you are actively using your working memory. Several scientific studies suggest that training of working memory has beneficial effects and can increase your cognitive functions.</description>
  <category>trivia</category>
  <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 07:19:47 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
